A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Vice President for Administration, Stuart K. Cassell, 1945-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- 1974
  - Garnett H. Johnston, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - J. Ambler Johnson Contribution, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - K-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Krebs, A.H., 1974 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard, Inc (3 folders), 1974 (Box 60, Folder 24-26)
  - Crawford, A.W., Business Manager Squires, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Mc-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Military- Army and Air Force, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Motor Pool, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - NCH Corporation-Lacy McClain, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - National Association of College and Business Officers(NACUBO), 1974 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, (NASULGC), 1974 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - NASULGC-Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - National Science Foundation, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Overtime-Authorized, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Physical Examinations, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Pollution (3 folders), 1974 (Box 61, Folder 5-7)
  - Quam, Dr. Mary E.- Summer School, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Research Park, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Reston, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Retirement, VA-Supplemental, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Reynolds Homestead, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Southern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Vepco Negotiating Team (2 folders), 1974 (Box 61, Folder 18-19)
  - VPI Facilities, INC, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Tech Union, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Veterinary Medicine, College of, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Water Authority, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Water Disposal-Dr. Lau, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - X,Y,Z Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Scholarships, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Student Aid and Matching Gifts, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Student Correspondence, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Sandra Sullivan Leave, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Student Government Association, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Telecommunications (2 folders), 1974 (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
  - Swink, H.W., 1974 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- 1975
  - University Council (5 folders), 1975 (Box 61, Folder 27-30, Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Building Committee, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Committee, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies and Research, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Football-Complimentary Tickets, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Day, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Inauguration Committee, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Rescue Squad, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Traffic Committee, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Search Committee for Vice President, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Lavery, W.E. (5 folders), 1975 (Box 62, Folder 14-18)
  - Brown, J. Gordon, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Bull, Fred W., 1975 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Burchard, Charles, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Burke, C.E., 1975 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Dean, James W. (4 folders), 1975 (Box 62, Folder 23-26)
  - Dean, James W., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Harper, Laura Jane, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Harvard, William C., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Hereford, Karl T., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Hill, David E. (2 folders), 1975 (Box 63, Folder 13-14)
  - Johnson, Overton, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Krebs, A.H., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Krebs, A.H.-Vice President for Special Projects, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Lacy, M.P., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Mitchell, H.H. (2 folders), 1975 (Box 63, Folder 19-20)
  - Robertson, R.M., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Ross, David L., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Skelton, W.E., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Smoot, Raymond D. Jr., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Talbot, Richard B., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Torgersen, Paul E., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Wilson, Coyt T., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Wilson, John O., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Bechanan, H. Gordon-Library, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Boone, J.F., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Butt, A.T., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Evans, E.B., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Gibson, O.L., Computing Center, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - King, H.P., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - McNeely, J.B.- Placement, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Montgomery, J.R., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Moseley, F.O., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Nickols, I.E. (2 folders), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 4-5)
  - Nunley, C.F., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Ridenour, Minnis E., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Russell, G.E., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Schiffert, C.W., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Shotts, J.E., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Sterrett, W.M. (2 folders), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 11-12)
  - Strother, W.H.(Others), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Wheeler, R.M., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - The Art Commission- Floyd E. Johnson, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Attorney General-Andrew P. Miller, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Division of Budget, John R. McCutcheon, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Comptroller, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings-H.D. Hamner. Jr., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Governor, Mills E. Godwin Jr., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Governors Executive Orders, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Division of Personnel, John W. Garber, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Property Records and Insurance, Stewart R. Moore, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Department of Treasury, Frank B. Miller Jr., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - State Council of Higher Education (2 folders), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 26-27)
  - State Highway Department, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - A-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Handbook, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Applications, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Airport Master Plan (2 folders), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 32-33)
  - Appalachian Power Company (2 folders), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 34-35)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Bands, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Blacksburg, Town of, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Budget Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Building Lockup, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - C-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Cable TV, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Capital Outlay-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Cassell, Stuart K., 1975 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Chatham Property, Pittsylania County, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - C and P Telephone Company, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Counseling Center, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - E-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Equal Opportunities Employment, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - F-Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1975 (Box 65, Folder 15-16)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Fireworks Display, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - First National Bank Exchange, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Founders Day, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - William M. Hahn Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Huffman, S.A., 1975 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - K-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Associates (3 folders), 1975 (Box 65, Folder 30-32)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Mc-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Military, General Acuff, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Motor Pool, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Myers, Anna Frances-Hearing, Employment, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - National Association of State Universities Land Grant Colleges, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - National Association of College and Universities Business Officers, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Overtime-Approved, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Health and Occupational Safety (2 folders), 1975 (Box 66, Folder 8-9)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Physical Examinations, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Research Park, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Reynolds Homestead, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Southern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Scholarships, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Student Government Association, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Southside VA Research Station Property, Charlotte County, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Space Guidelines, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Squires-Central Accounting for Students, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Special Academic Programs-Dr. Edwin and Martha Harder, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Student Aid, H.H. McEver (2 folders), 1975 (Box 66, Folder 24-25)
  - Student Correspondence (2 folders), 1975 (Box 66, Folder 26-27)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Telecommunications, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Tech Union, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - VPI Facilities, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Water Authority, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - White Papers, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Wise, M.B., 1975 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - X,Y,Z Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Henderson, D.S., 1975 (Box 68, Folder 17)